work-from-home-concepts.com 2012-12-02

# Work-from-Home Concepts

Work-from-Home Concepts reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. The date and time of the last update will always appear below which serves as notice to our visitors and members. This website is for informational purposes only. It does not guarantee employment.

Last Updated: May 10, 2012, 9:26 p.m. CST

MEMBER INFORMATION

Collection of Information  
Email addresses are collected by but not limited to those who opt in to receive our newsletter, replies to posts or posts comments on our forums, or contacts us via email. Email addresses or any other information volunteered by a visitor is not share with any other organization.

How We Your Email Address:  
Email address will be used for corresponding email, sending newsletters, and other correspondence. If you chose not to receive any communication from Work-from-Home Concepts, please select the unsubscribe link found at the footer of this website or in any emails you may have received from us. 

Cookies will not be used; however, there are third-party advertising ads posted throughout this website. These advertisers may use your browsing history to send you offers based on the data they collect and is used at their discretion. They will not collect any personal information such as your name, address, email address, or phone number. Visitors who opt in with their email address can request a description of how their email address or any information volunteered by the visitor is used by emailing their request to [info@work-from-home-concepts.com](mailto:info@work-from-home-concepts.com).

Any additional means of use of Member’s information will be published on this Privacy Policy and effective as soon as it is posted on this website and will be notified of changes via email notification in order to give you an opportunity to opt out if you choose.

Registration to Other Sites  
Members have access to links to other sites and can choose to register for other site during their visit to our site. Once a Member clicks on any link and registers to that site, member’s user information may be shared with that site’s advertisers. Members are not required to select any of these sites or click on any links to that site.

Other Website’s and Their Privacy Policies  
This website contains links to third party websites. We provide these links for your convenience, but we do not review, control or monitor their privacy practices. Work-from-Home Concepts is not responsible for the operation of these websites or for any interaction you have with them. By clicking on any third party link, you are agreeing to the terms and conditions of those websites, including the privacy policy.

 Where to Contact Me  
If you have questions or comments about our Privacy Policy, if you prefer not to receive information about any products or services or any other questions in general, please send me an email at [cramos@work-from-home-concepts.com](mailto:cramos@work-from-home-concepts.com).
